Contact

9565636619 (Mobile) linda.nnajiofor@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dr-lindannajiofor-dnp-aprn-np-c-7a3007b0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Healthcare Management
Hospitals

Certifications

Neonatal Resuscitation Program Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP) BLS

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Advanced Practice Registered Nurse

Dr. Linda Nnajiofor, DNP, APRN, NP-C

Family Nurse Practitioner at Signify Health Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Board Certified Family Nurse Practitioner who enjoys providing exceptional patient care in busy, diverse healthcare environments. Throughout my career, I've honed the ability to independently assess, diagnose, monitor, and treat a variety of illnesses and conditions to improve patients' quality of life. Further, I've earned respect as an influential leader and collaborator with clinical expertise in primary care, emergency services, urgent care, palliative care and home health.

I'm known for educating patients and caregivers on the options, goals, and expected outcomes of treatment plans with the utmost level of compassion and professionalism. As an out-of-the-box thinker, I remain committed to continuously identify and implement the safest, most effective therapeutic regimen to optimize treatment outcomes.

In addition to my professional experience, I have exemplary educational qualifications, including my Doctorate of Nursing Practice with Family Nurse Practitioner from the University of the Incarnate Word, combined with multiple licenses and certifications.

Experience

Signify Health
Family Nurse Practitioner
February 2020 - Present (5 months)

Memorial Hermann Health System Emergency Room Registered Nurse February 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) United States Padilla Medical Clinic
Family Nurse Practitioner Practicum
June 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 7 months)
Houston, Texas

SHARY GARDENS PEDIATRICS Family Nurse Practitioner Practicum June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months) Mission, Texas, United States

WOMANKIND OBGYN ASSOCIATES

Family Nurse Practitioner Practicum February 2019 - April 2019 (3 months) McAllen, Texas, United States

Methodist Children's Hospital ER Travel Nurse December 2017 - January 2018 (2 months)

Paxvilla Hospice
Registered Nurse Case Manager
January 2016 - January 2018 (2 years 1 month)
McAllen, Texas, United States

University Hospital San Antonio ER Travel Registered Nurse August 2017 - December 2017 (5 months) San Antonio, Texas

Epic Health Services, Inc.
Private Duty Nurse
June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months)
San Antonio, Texas

Children's Hospital of San Antonio Emergency Room Registered Nurse November 2016 - April 2017 (6 months) San Antonio, Texas

Edinburg Regional Medical Ctr Emergency Room Registered Nurse

August 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 4 months)

Edinburg, Texas

Edinburg Children's Hospital Emergency Room Registered Nurse August 2015 - November 2016 (1 year 4 months) Edinburg, Texas

DHR Health Nurse Tech June 2014 - July 2015 (1 year 2 months) Edinburg, Texas, United States

Education

University of the Incarnate Word

Doctorate of Nursing Practice, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2017 - 2019)

The University of Texas Rio Grande Valley Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing (2013 - 2015)

Texas Woman's University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Pre-Nursing Studies · (2011 - 2012)